

VADYM HOPKO

Front-End Developer

ABOUT ME

I was born on August 10, 1990. Front-End for me is both a job and a hobby, so even in my off-hours I am engaged in development. I like to create the most convenient interaction between users and website or web-application. I plan to become a Senior Front-End Developer in a 5 years

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Git
- Gulp
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- SVG
- Node.js
- jQuery
- Figma
- English Pre-Intermediate

CONTACT

Email: gopko.vadim@gmail.com Phone: +1(808)-428-57-81

Website: vadymhopko.github.io/portfolio Address: 665 Kapaia street, Honolulu HI 96825

WORK EXPERIENCE

Vice-rector's assistant

I.I. Mechnikov Odesa National University | January 2014 - January 2015

- Created student organizations
- Accepted appeals to the Vice-rector
- Worked on the preparation of meetings and sessions held by the Vice-rector

Top manager

Interwindows, engineering company | February 2020 - June 2021

- Presented the company's services to developers
- Made commercial offers

Freelancer

Vip orders - Freelance websites | January 2022 - December 2022

- Web/Mobile design
- Responsive websites development
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Setting up hosting and domain name

EDUCATION

I.I. Mechnikov Odesa National University Expert | 2007 - 2012

- Faculty of Economics and Law
- Specialty: "Jurisprudence"
- Qualification: "Lawyer"

COURSES

Hillel IT School

FrontEnd Developer | 2021 - 2021

- Course Front-End Basic | March 2021 June 2021
- Course Front-End Pro | August 2021 December 2021

Graduate Certificates

- https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/97046686
- https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/86477844